https://wrestlepundit.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: https://wrestlepundit.com.
What personal data we collect and why
Email
If you contact us we may collect the email address you use and any other identifying information you provide, such as a name or online alias.
Please do not give us other personal or sensitive information.
Comments
We do not collect any personal data through the commenting process on this website. The commenting system on this site is handled by Disqus. You should refer to their sign-up terms and privacy policy to see what data they may collect and how this may be used.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles and posts on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, social media content, images, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
If you choose to “like” or “share” information from this website through these services, you should review the privacy policy of that service. If you are a member of a social media site, the interfaces may allow the social media site to connect your visits to this site with other Personal Information.
Our website also contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When you go to other websites from here, we advise you to be aware and read their privacy policy.
Cookies
To improve your experience on our site or in the process of delivering personalised ads, we and our partners may use ‘cookies’. Cookies are an industry standard and most major websites use them. A cookie is a small text file that our site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences and browsing information. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.
Analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google’s Privacy Policy and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.
Third Party Advertisers
We use third-party advertising companies, including Google AdSense, to display ads on some of our pages. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
Specifically, the DoubleClick cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser.
You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
You can review Google’s privacy policy regarding advertising here and its partner sites here. These pages also provide information on how to manage what information is collected and how to opt out of collection.
The Chris Benoit Files
WrestlePundit
Popular Posts Chris Benoit Conspiracies Debunked
A History of Drugs in WWE
Tweets by @wrestlingnews
Partner Site WideShut.co.uk - alternative news and views
Copyright © 2019 | Contact | Privacy Policy | Sitemap
We use 'cookies' to analyse and measure traffic to this site. Cookies also are used by advertisers to serve ads that are personalised to your interests or browsing habits. If you agree to the use of cookies click 'I Agree' or to learn more, read our: Privacy PolicyI Agree
We use 'cookies' to analyse and measure traffic to this site. Cookies also are used by advertisers to serve ads that are personalised to your interests or browsing habits. If you agree to the use of cookies click 'I Agree' or to learn more, read our: Privacy PolicyI Agree
